Class of 1947 Records, 1943-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1947 Records
1943-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1947.
RG 80 UUID:94317208-2ffa-44c9-b773-bec8e2d958fe
13 boxes (16 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1947.
The Class of 1947 was the sixty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1947 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1947, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, treasury information, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1947 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1947 (Box 2159, Folder 1)
- Commencement-Music 1947 (Box 2159, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Photographs 1947 (Box 2159, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Speaker 1947 (Box 2159, Folder 4)
- Freshman Handbook 1943-1944 (Box 2159, Folder 5)
- General 1943-1944 (Box 2159, Folder 6)
- Groups 1943-1947, 1981 (Box 2159, Folder 7)
- Hoop Rolling 1947 (Box 2159, Folder 8)
- Ivy Day 1947 (Box 2159, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1947 (Box 2159, Folder 10)
- Junior Prom 1946 (Box 2159, Folder 11)
- Junior Ushers 1946 (Box 2159, Folder 12)
- Class Letters 1957-1994 (Box 2159, Folder 13)
- Officers 1943-1947 (Box 2159, Folder 14)
- Questionnaire 1967 (Box 2159, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 2159, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1952 (Box 2159, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1957 (Box 2159, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1962 (Box 2159, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 2159, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 2159, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1977-1982 (Box 2159, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1987 (Box 2159, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1992 (Box 2159, Folder 24)
- Reunions 1997-2002 (Box 2159, Folder 25)
- Reunion Songs 1952 (Box 2159, Folder 26)
- Songs undated (Box 2159, Folder 27)
- Sophomore Carnival 1945 (Box 2159, Folder 28)
- Step Sings 1947 (Box 2159, Folder 29)
- Class Supper 1947 (Box 2159, Folder 30)
- Treasurer 1962-1998 (Box 2159, Folder 31)